oceanspray.com 2017-11-22

# Tastes Good, Good For You® Cranberry Juices & Snacks | Ocean Spray

**Ocean Spray Privacy Policy (US)**

In this Privacy Policy:

**Ocean Spray** refers to Ocean Spray Cranberries, Inc.

**Website refers** to this website, [www.oceanspray.com](http://www.oceanspray.com/).

Ocean Spray Cranberries, Inc. ("we", "us", or "our") is committed to protecting your personal privacy. This policy applies to Ocean Spray Cranberries, Inc. and describes our information practices, whether such information is provided to us via our stores, head office, this Website, or other means, and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on this Website. This policy forms part of our Legal Terms of Use, which you should also read, for use of this Website and other websites operated by us in the US. To make this policy easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Some of our sites may be directed in whole or in part to children under the age of 13. Our policy regarding these sites and instances where children's personal information may be collected is described below under the heading "Children's Privacy Policy."

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or our Children's Privacy Policy, you can Contact Us by e-mail, phone, or letter. We'll be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.

This Policy applies only to Ocean Spray websites on which it is posted, and it does not apply to banners, sweepstakes, and other advertisements or promotions that we may sponsor or participate in on websites owned by third parties.

###  Your Consent to This Privacy Policy

By using this site, you signify that you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as our Legal Terms of Use. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy or our Terms of Use, please do not use this site or provide any Personal Information to us. From time to time, this site may change, and/or our practices with respect to how we collect, use, or otherwise treat personally identifiable information may change. We reserve the right to update or change this Privacy Policy at our discretion. We will post any changes to this Policy or any new policy here and we encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed. If there is any material change in the type of information we collect or the way in which we use such information, we will comply with any applicable laws with respect to notifying you of those changes, or where legally necessary, obtaining your consent to those changes.

###  The Information We Collect

Ocean Spray will not collect any personally-identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means that we do not require you to register or provide information to us in order to view any of our sites. You might provide information to us if you: 

  * Contact our Consumer Services Team;
  * Participate in our promotions, prize draws, and competitions;
  * Subscribe to our publications or communications from us; or
  * Register to become a member of the Cranberry Club.

The information we collect from you may include, but is not limited to, your name, gender, address, date of birth, e-mail address, and your product purchases and purchase history. If necessary, Ocean Spray may also ask you to provide it with additional personal information from time to time, including when you contact our Consumer Services Team.

You are never required to provide Ocean Spray with your personal information, but failure to provide information may result in Ocean Spray's inability to provide you with the information, goods, or services you have requested. If you wish to communicate with us anonymously or by using a pseudonym, you may do so. However, if may be impracticable in some circumstances, for example if you wish to participate in a promotion.

###  Use of Your Personal Information

Ocean Spray collects, uses, and discloses your personal information for a range of purposes, such as those listed above. When you supply Personal Information on this site, we will use it for the purpose for which it was collected (e.g. to enter you in a sweepstakes or loyalty program, or to fulfill the delivery of a sweepstakes prize or product order or to send you information regarding our products and promotions). If you specifically agree to follow-up contacts by us or ask to be put on our mailing list when you register, we may contact you from time to time. You can always change your preference for follow-up contacts or opt out of any further contacts or services just by e-mailing us at any time or by visiting the area of the site where you registered. However, unless you specifically register to receive communication from a site, that site will not contact you.

The Website may also collect Personal Information from you about a third party (e.g., the site might allow you to send an e-mail or message to a friend, in which case we will need that person's name and e-mail address.) Please note that we use such information only for the specified purpose (e.g. to deliver the e-mail message) and we will not contact the third party again by e-mail unless you request us to, if they have an existing business relationship with us, or the third party contacts us.

###  Collection and Use of Other Information; Cookies

When you visit our Website or download information from it, our Internet Service Provider makes a record of your visit and records the following: 

  * Your internet address (IP address);
  * The type of Internet browser you are using;
  * Domain names, if applicable; and
  * The date and time of your visit to the Website.

We use this data to analyze trends and statistics. This Website also uses cookies and Google Analytics service, which evaluates your use of this Website. Most Web browsers can be configured to notify the user when a cookie is received, allowing you to either accept or reject it. In addition, you may choose to disable or block the cookies, whether from Ocean Spray or Google, by selecting the appropriate setting on your browser. Refusal of cookies at sites you enter may result in an inability to visit certain areas of the Website or to receive personalized information and content when you visit the Website. You may also download and install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on available on the Google website.

###  With Whom We May Share Information

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we don't share the information you give us with anyone outside of the Ocean Spray family of companies. In certain instances, we may disclose your personally-identifiable information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities that may be causing injury to you, Ocean Spray, or others. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it. In the event of a merger, consolidation or sale or transfer of all or substantially all of our company or its assets, it is possible that all user information collected by this site will be transferred to the purchaser or the new company.

###  Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors

We may, from time to time, offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties, including affiliated businesses. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the Website activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of information. Since these third parties will use your information in accordance with their own privacy policies and practices, you should check their websites for information regarding their privacy policies. We will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

We may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at our Web Pages. These third-party ad servers may use cookies, Web beacons, clear .gifs, or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third-party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We and our advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on the Website and to conduct research about the advertisements.

###  Questionnaires and Surveys

From time to time, our sites may also be conducting questionnaires and surveys. Survey information will be treated like all of the information we collect, and it is used to help us improve the appeal of our products and our Website.

###  Security

Ocean Spray takes reasonable steps to protect your personal information from misuse, interference and loss, and from unauthorized access, modification, or disclosure. We do this by means of various physical and electronic security measures, including restricting physical access to our offices and implementing a number of technological and security policies and procedures. Notwithstanding the foregoing, no data transmission over the internet is totally secure and we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. As a result, any personal information you send to Ocean Spray over the Internet (including via e-mail) is sent at your own risk.

If we no longer require your personal information for the purpose for which this information was collected, we will take all steps reasonable in the circumstances to destroy the information (unless we are required by law to retain this information) or ensure that the information is de-identified.

###  Accessing and Updating Your Information

You may request details of the personal information we hold about you by contacting us via any of the methods listed here. We will respond to your request within a reasonable period of time and we will give you access to the information in the manner requested by you if it is reasonable and practicable to do so.

In general, we will allow you access to your personal information, unless a specific exception applies, and will take such steps as are reasonable to provide you with the information in the form you require. If we deny you access to any personal information following an access request or provide you with access not in a manner requested by you, we will give you a written notice that will set out the reasons for the denial and the mechanisms available to you to complain about our refusal.

We will not charge any fee for the provision of this information, except when we are required to spend an unreasonable amount of time or effort to provide you with the information. If there is a charge, it will not be excessive and will not apply to the making of the request.

We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is accurate, up-to-date, and complete. If you are aware that any of your personal information is inaccurate, out-of-date, or incomplete, please inform us by calling our toll-free hotline at 1-800-662-3263 so that we can update our records. If you make a request to correct your personal information, we will respond to your request within a reasonable period. We will not charge any fee for making the request or for correcting your personal information.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

###  Links to Other Sites

Our Website may contain links to other sites, such as Facebook or Twitter, that are not operated by us and whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.  

###  Children’s Privacy Policy

_Children’s Privacy Policy – General_

Generally, Ocean Spray and the [www.oceanspray.com](http://www.oceanspray.com/) Website do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 on this site, do not direct this site to children under 13, and do not believe that our site is appealing to children in that age group.

If you are under the age of 13, we request that you do not provide any personally identifiable information to us. If Ocean Spray becomes aware that it has received unsolicited personal information from children under 13, we will promptly terminate any accounts associated with such information and delete any and all such personal information. If you are a parent and believe your child has provided us with information, please contact Ocean Spray at:

[**Click here**](https://ask.oceanspray.com/contact-us/) to use our email form.

**Call Us**  
Toll-Free at 1-800-662-3263  
Weekdays, 9:00 a.m. – 6:00 p.m. Eastern Standard Time

**Write Us**  
Ocean Spray Cranberries  
Consumer Affairs  
Post Office Box 2253  
Kings Mountain, NC 28086

_Children’s Privacy Policy for Promotions, Sweepstakes, and Competitions_

From time to time, however, we may request limited personally-identifiable information in order to conduct online contests or sweepstakes. Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), Ocean Spray will never knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without first obtaining verifiable consent from the child's parent or legal guardian. Our practices with respect to collection of personally-identifiable information from children under the age of 13 are described below. We do not condition a child's participation in an activity on the child's disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to engage in the activity. In addition, a parent may at any time review and edit any personally-identifiable information collected about their child under the age of 13, have this information deleted, and prohibit further collection or use of the child's information (although this may require the child to forfeit any prize won in a sweepstakes or contest).

###  Updates to This Privacy Policy

From time to time, we reserve the right to make updates to this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by, for example, placing a notice on this Website. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Website following any changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such change.

###  Important Note Regarding U.S. Law Use of Materials on this Website

Please note: The laws and regulations in different countries impose different (and even conflicting) requirements on the Internet and data protection. All matters relating to this Website are governed by the laws of the State of Delaware in the USA. If you are located outside the USA, including in the European Economic Area, and you contact us, please not that any information you provide will be transferred to the USA and by submitting the information you authorize this transfer and understand that the information you provide will be protected as provided under U.S. law, not the law of your home country.
